<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Maps</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_close">CloseActivity</string>
    <string name="clues">Clues</string>
    <string name="rules">Rules</string>
    <string name="looking_for_clues">Look for clues...</string>
    <string name="title_activity_clues2">Clues2Activity</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="location">Location</string>
    <string-array name="weapons_array">
        <item>butcherknife</item>
        <item>arrow</item>
        <item>chandelier</item>
        <item>revolver</item>
        <item>rope</item>
        <item>leadpipe</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="suspects_array">
        <item>Dr. Mustard</item>
        <item>Janitor Green</item>
        <item>Dean Plum</item>
        <item>Scarlet</item>
        <item>Nurse White</item>
        <item>Dr. Peacock</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="suspects">Suspects</string>
    <string name="dr_white">Dr. White</string>
    <string name="janitor_green">Janitor Green</string>
    <string name="weapons">Weapons</string>
    <string name="crime_scene">Crime Scene</string>

    <string name="title_activity_splash">SplashActivity</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="mystery_at_maynooth">Mystery at Maynooth</string>
    <string name="play">Play</string>
    <string name="what_happened">What happened...</string>
    <string name="goBack">Go back</string>
    <string name="ruleText">To win, you must visit all 13 locations on the map of Maynooth. They will
        be marked with red circles before you visit them, and marked green after you visit them. Each
        location will either identify itself as the crime scene, or eliminate a weapon or suspect.\n\t
        Once you have visited all locations, return to the location identified as the crime scene
        and fill in the suspect and weapon which you DID NOT find at any location. </string>
    <string name="storyText">In the middle of the night, you awake with a start to the sound of a blood-
        curdling scream in the distance. Frightened, you make sure that your door and window are locked.
        You peer out the window, but see nothing, and return to bed uneasily. The next morning, you
        still wonder what the source of the scream was. You wish that you could ask your flatmates if they
        heard anything, but campus is almost entirely empty since it is study week. \n\tOn the way to the library,
        you see a number of Gardai, which is peculiar. After seeing a fifth garda, you stop to ask
        why there are so many on campus. He answers \"Oh, just some rowdy kids. Nothing to worry about.\"
        You\'re certain that there\'s a cover-up going on, since the last time you saw even one garda in
        Maynooth was- Well, long enough ago that you can\'t recall.\n\t
        There\'s a murderer on the loose, and only you can stop him.</string>
</resources>
